[Music]
thank you
hello and welcome to morning trade with
money control I'm karunyarao and I'm
here to help you navigate the trading
day with actionable strategies sectoral
Trends and most importantly your queries
during the show so please keep
commenting on our live feed we'll have
your questions addressed towards the end
of the show but let's get started and
see what the global Handover looks like
Europe close higher as the region felt
the impact of UK's fiscal u-turns and
anticipated new EU measures to tackle
Energy prices stock 600 index Rose by
0.4 percent towards the end of the
session as all major buses logged in
games
Wall Street rallies for the second
straight day indices gain about a
percent in a choppy session with
earnings leading the markets higher
stocks in the Asia Pacific region trade
higher as well following a strong
Handover from Wall Street for a second
day on the Trot sgx Nifty however is
indicating a higher start for the Indian
market
for lesson City sector continue to be
marred by input cost inflation even in
Q2 we get you a detailed preview ahead
of key consumer earnings lined up this
week also in the spotlight are adani
Enterprises ICICI Lombard and praj
industries
all right let's talk markets then bring
on board our technical expert for the
day him in kapadia from KR choksi
morning amen and thanks for joining in
how's the setup looking and will you be
also uh betting on that positive start
to sustain for the Indian markets
a very good morning thank you for having
me uh I think yes a positive start
because we spent almost six hours
yesterday Colonial consolidating after
the Kappa now two things we've had a
bullish Gap a market has a tendency to
cover up caps caronia now we haven't
done that to
yesterday obviously uh we don't look
like doing that today but in the next
few trading sessions or in next four
five trading sessions one gets the
feeling that we might just make an
attempt to cover up this Gap but yes the
setup like you mentioned is good the
weeks is below 18 that's a big big uh
positive for the market and yes uh I
mean you've seen Market breadth
improving the mid caps have recovered
you know Market leaders like Reliance
have started looking positive on the
chart so Frankly Speaking everything
seems decently set yes but I wouldn't
like to chase the gap of Corona from
that point of view but yes I think the
setup seems good the bank Nifty is
leading and it seems to it and Reliance
I think other two pillars for the market
to go ahead and not to forget Banks yeah
and Reliance definitely this week will
be in the Limelight on you know the back
of numbers that are going to come out
later this week but let's talk about
some more individual names that could be
in the spotlight on back of news flow
and earnings the first one I want to
highlight is adani Enterprises now it's
subsidiary company adani defense systems
has planned to acquire air works for an
Enterprise value of 400 crore rupees in
fact the company has already signed a
definitive agreement to acquire this uh
entity called air works now let's talk
about the technicals of adani
Enterprises and how are they positioned
what is the likely move in days to come
seem to be clearly a range from nine
trading sessions uh in a range between
three one one zero on the downside and
uh 3338 on the upside nine trading
sessions no directional bias uh but yes
that's uh they can we can consider what
can be a hint of a relative strength
coming in the 60 Minutes 120 minutes and
180 minutes charts are turning positive
50 can support on the 55 day exponential
moving average but you need to take out
Ok well I want to flag off a few
earnings candidates as well on our radar
ICICI Lombard is one of them uh their
queue to profit has seen a growth of 32
percent year on year coming in at 590
crore rupees net premium that the the
insurer has earned has also jumped 18 by
y coming in at 3 800 odd crore rupees
let's talk about ICICI Lombard yesterday
it shuts up in the green firmly in the
green but what's the way forward in the
next few weeks uh do you do you expect
some more positive momentum on this
counter
in fact it is one of my picks for the
day also uh We've formed a base over
here uh the volume has improved so while
uh it is forming a base a volume has
gradually picked up the mechanical
indicators have given crossover buys
some after reflecting positive
Divergence so Vic I mean this is a daily
picture the VT I mean we need the
positives to percolate on the weekly
also so having said that a short-term
water I believe has been made unless
1120 breaks so that doesn't look like
happening so short-term bottom seems to
be made and we're looking we are at 11
for 50 you know we should gravitate
towards uh 1180 and then 1200 so short
term the picture has definitely improved
medium term we are looking at a bounce
but we'll have to see how it handles the
resistance levels
okay right the next earnings candidate I
want to flag off is praj Industries uh
uh interesting stock from the broad
markets lot of interest among trading
Community as well Q2 profit has searched
44 this time around coming in at 48
crores largely backed by healthy Revenue
growth good operating income growth as
well Revenue in fact if you look at it
is up almost 65 percent here on year uh
let's talk about the chart of praj
Industries then and how it's positioned
actually we we have undergone or we are
undergoing a prolonged period of
consolidation
17 months and Counting large range
between 290 on the downside and 450 on
the upside and it is sort of training at
the niche so to speak it's on the verge
of breaking out from here we would need
a weekly close above 450 which I believe
uh it almost happened a couple of weeks
back but to be pinpoint precise it's
never happened in a solicit history so
after 17 months in the stock closes up
of 450 on the VT breaks out from here I
believe uh 500 would be a cinch we
should be moving gradually towards 550
so looks good major consolidation seems
set for a Breakout
okay all right uh he may request you to
stay on with us I love I'll just touch
base with my colleague from moneycontrol
Pro to talk about the fmcg stocks and
the sector at large slew of earnings
lined up this week starting from Nestle
to ITC and of course uh you know some of
the names from the small and mid cap of
universe as well
um nandish hi morning and thanks for
joining in
what we are given to understand from a
host of reports is that consumption
environment largely remains weak in Q2
more or less similar to what we saw in
q1 how about the inflation Factor has
that eased or do we see some pain in Q2
earnings as well because of the
volatility and the uptick we've seen in
in most commodity prices
hi good morning and thanks for having me
yeah uh in Q2 we might uh we will be
seeing the inflation pressures uh
because uh usually the companies have
been carrying a high cost inventory
which will be utilized in the September
quarter so in this quarter we also
expect the margin process to proceed
like
like the June quarter
but uh now that a lot of these commodity
prices have started to uh cool off their
easing a fair bit by when can we expect
that to reflect in the earnings will
second half be better for fmcg stocks uh
fmcg companies vis-a-vis first half
we expect the margins to recover in the
second half of fy23 uh especially the
players uh which are consuming palm oil
because palm oil is almost corrected by
more than 40 percent
but what you say recently we have seen
that the wheat prices have again started
warming up and they are I guess Higher
by more than 15 in last 15 20 days so uh
the margin pressures uh will ease of
what you say by second half but uh the
players especially consuming uh uh what
is the sugar in wheat might see some
pressure still
and what about rural versus Urban demand
scenario uh is rural still looking
weaker than Urban and does that mean
that we should focus on stocks that have
less exposure to rural markets perhaps
yeah even in September quarter we have
seen that the rural does not recovered
but uh what do you say going on the
basis of what we have seen uh in the
month of September uh especially with
the buying of the festive season and
with good normal monsoons we expect the
rural to recover uh what do you say by
second half of 523 so uh we can still
focus on players who are more exposed
towards the rural segment
okay all right so uh do we have any
preferred list of stocks or companies
that look like that that are strongly
positioned for this quarter earnings
that you guys are betting on will
deliver good results despite all that is
going on
yeah uh uh coming to our preferred list
uh we continue to prefer ITC at uh even
at these levels uh what is that despite
the out performance against the fmcg bug
uh what is fmcg basket another good pick
from the fmcg is uh currently Varun
beverages uh even we like ITC uh we like
working beverages we like dabur and we
like uh what is consumer Foods consumer
products okay so from the large cap
Universe it's mainly ITC and of course
God's Rich consumer and Varun beverages
then uh in
watch out for uh for the sector in in
the days to come apart from uh what we
discussed
see if you would you say recently since
uh some of the Commodities again
hardening so in case
is persist for another quarter
then we are in terms of risk of earnings
okay all right nandish thank you so much
for joining in and flagging a flagging
off
of Tim Q2 earnings and beyond that and
stocks to keep on your radar as far as
this quarter's earnings performance is
concerned all right moving back on hey
main is still standing by so let's bring
him on board he made any of these smcg
names that you like this week a lot of
earnings are going to come out
um and nandish was just talking about
the fundamental aspect that ITC gcpl uh
you know Varun beverages these names are
looking attractive but from a technical
standpoint any favorites that you have
I think even my preference would be
something on similar lines with what he
said uh ITC is looking promising we've
had a I mean after years of you know
under performance we've seen ITC you
know sort of ticket Place in the Sun but
now uh despite the one we move we've
gone up virtually from two one zero to
350. it's taken seven eight months but
it's virtually Veena one way more but
despite that uh it looks technically set
up uh the technical setup seems fine
beverage is slightly corrective we were
is consolidating daba takes some time to
move but as of now it's ITC there is
resistance at around 355 but uh on any
ranking short medium long term whatever
time frame you look at we are in an
established uptrend and it looks like
continuing to do so so Frankly Speaking
a few couple of months down the line I
would be surprised of ITC is is at a
fresh altamine
okay all right moving on then let's also
address some of our viewers questions
and comments uh that are coming in since
you were talking about you know the
consumption pack we have a query on ITC
and if you could give us a target range
on cell this is a question from Monica
most people are optimistic about ITC but
would you have a target range to sell it
as well
uh well Monica Frankly Speaking I don't
see any technical reasons for itself uh
it's formed a small a very small
rounding bottom in the daily chart which
is basically a bullish formation the the
move yesterday is on to Pro more than
two crochets in AC cash Market that is
higher than the last five seven trading
sessions indicators are in buy mode on
the daily chart on the monthly chart so
Frankly Speaking I don't see uh I mean
I'm assuming a sale is a short no I
don't see any uh I don't see any signals
to short the stock in fact it seems to
be moving towards 350 and more so no
current as of now as I see the charts
today I don't change cell signals in ITC
especially for for a shot
okay all right let's talk about some
more queries and questions um
thing to us and he wants your advice on
aircon for the short term how how is it
how's the chart looking
okay I am assuming the short term would
be probably a few trading sessions so uh
as of now we've had a move from 38.6 to
45. it's tired or we are undergoing a
cool off uh so Frankly Speaking time
being it's taking a breather uh 41.8 is
support I don't expect anything much
unless and until it closes up a 43.8
okay all right next query is from Aditya
he wants you to guide him on a car trade
he entered the counter at 1319 rupees
levels and wants to know whether he
should hold or sell at the current
levels clearly the stock has slipped a
fair bit from those levels right now
sub 600 rupees in fact it slipped quite
a bit uh you know in the last uh one
month if we look at it September highs
of seven seven sixteen Seven Seventeen
it has given up more than 200 rupees on
the downside do you think the downtrend
could continue and one it's better if
one exits at these levels and cuts their
losses
I think so karunya most of these new age
businesses whether it's uh Nike up ATM
cartridge
maybe even zomato many of these have
disappointed
and cartrade is same at 550 we have a
strong medium term support but I don't
think this is enough for a reversal it
remains in a downtrend uh and after the
sideways move between 550 and 7 40 7 35
it looks set to continue further so I
have a feeling that
despite a slight oversold situation on
the daily chart I don't see anything
which seems to suggest that uh cartrade
will reverse majorly supported 550 yes
maybe he can wait to see 550 works and
provides the uh you know a setup for a
bounce to reduce his losses but no I I
think he'll have to book a loss later
now or waiting to see 550 and then a
possible deal
okay all right makes sense uh another
question this is also from uh for the
consumption space aarti is writing to us
and she wants your view for the short
term on Tata consumer how's the stock
looking
uh
data consumer okay firstly okay short
term the bias is positive period 734 I
believe we'd probably see 788 in the
next few trading sessions but despite
her short-term view uh I just 30 seconds
I take a slightly longer term view one
year and Counting don't move it
consolidation on the long term after a
brilliant run short-term bias for a few
trading sizes
okay all right
moving on another query on Tata Group
Company hey month jaju is writing to us
he wants your view on Tata lxc
following a deep cut in the stock he's
asking whether to book uh more or exit
what do you suggest
well if the stock moves from 500 to 10
800. I think you can't run two marathons
in a row so honestly speaking I believe
the move is over for the timing we
walked into a correction of a greater
degree uh yeah we're off from ten
thousand seven hundred to seven thousand
two hundred in in three straight months
and uh I don't think that changes so
it's probably a sell-on bounce I think
it's gonna take some time to recover
simply because it had a humongous
phenomenal move
all right next query then uh this is
coming in from vasu and he wants your
view on the banking sector I'm assuming
it's the banking index he's asking about
and he's also um flag or flagged off a
few individual names Access Federal and
SBI so if you could tell us how each of
them stack up against one another and if
there's any clear winner here
okay briefly I'll just run through the
bank Nifty of 40 500 resistance uh we
are in a short term uptrend which might
get converted into a medium term of
trend uh we need to close over 40 500 to
see 41 600 the three stocks that you
mentioned SBI Federal and axis Bank
Federal is the strongest of the lot I I
can't think of any of the stocks which
are posted a fresh on time when I
Federal hash so we remain safely and
it's constant or medium short term and
longer term operate all-time highs
expected to continue State Bank if PSU
banks are going to recover straightway
has to be in the hell looking good looks
set to post refresh all-time high but
the ones talk which I kept for the last
is access bank it's a very interesting
scenario uh
permit me 15 seconds
we've been here for 18 months uh between
6 20 on the downside 820 on the upside
we are at around 816. we've never closed
above 860 on the monthly chart in the
history listed history of access bank if
it does you're looking at a minimum 100
Point upside so I mean it depends on the
uh the strategy of the investor if you
want to look at a big chunk but it's not
yet confirmed access bank if you want to
go for something which is already in the
third or the fifth year fifth year is
federal bank and uh State Bank is
somewhere Midway my pick would be access
bank so it's not yet breaking out but
the breakout comes in it's going to
provide handsome returns
okay all right
um next query is 4p Delight uh sudha is
asking if uh you know it will continue
its uh strength in terms of technicals
uh it's still uh close to its 52-week
high it has school of a dad but but I
don't I don't know if one should be
worried at these levels what do you say
no absolutely I don't think one needs to
be worried it's in some
and they still haven't changed so yes uh
there's not nothing to suggest a worry
on Pedialyte on technical parameters
from a medium to long term point of you
know seems Seems safe in an uptrend okay
all right uh very quickly then funny is
messaging us he wants your advice on
Hindustan Unilever whether it's a hold
or a cell at these levels he's not given
us his entry point but uh the stock very
flatish last one month uh do you see the
sluggishness sustain
15 weeks of a sideways movement so I
think very valid question yes I think
you pointed it out nicely sluggish and I
think it's expected to remain sluggish
Until It Breaks out on the Range
down third is 25 26 upside is 21
32. anybody's guess after 15 weeks which
side it breaks out having said that it
doesn't look technically negative yet it
seems to be consolidating in an up move
but yes for this to fructify we need a
cloth about 27 30.
okay all right the last query then
quickly adarsh is posting a comment he
wants to know how adani pots could
perform in the coming days what is your
reading
set for about short-term bottom seem to
be made at 771 uh short-term bias
turning positive resistance at 8 30
closable 830 V3 860. looks good set to
appreciate further stop loss needs to be
kept at night okay I mean you already
flagged off that ICICI Lombard is one
stock that you're very optimistic about
what is the other stock uh you want to
highlight it to our viewers now
yeah the other stock is uh
uh Finance uh the stock is looking
technically interesting we seem to have
formed the base over here uh the weekly
mechanical indicators have all given
crossover buys uh we've been
consolidating for around eight and a
half weeks now uh and it started making
the right noises on the daily chart we
should over we should be ready to
overcome the 55-day moving average
either today or tomorrow and
the breakout comes in at uh around 1068.
so by uh Finance return one zero four
zero stop loss one zero one five Target
one zero nine zero it's a slightly
modest Target it has the propensity it
has a capacity to overshoot
okay and uh just before we let you go
I'm seeing a lot of questions coming in
uh on kpit so if you could quickly give
us your take
okay I think the time frame matters if
you have a long term point of view uh
this stock is heading towards four
figures now short-term point of view
we've been consolidating between 635 and
690 for around 19 trading session so no
directional bias weekly chart says it's
a it's a cool off in the midst of an
update
okay very well for thank you so much him
in on that note for joining in and
sharing with us your readings of uh the
market and a host of stocks with that
it's a wrap on morning trade thank you
for tuning in
[Music]
foreign